triumph.com 2015-06-23

# Privacy Statement - Triumph Official Store

Last Updated: October 1, 2013

PRIVACY STATEMENT

Triumph of Europe, Inc. (" **Triumph** ") are committed to protecting the privacy of all individuals who utilize this website (the " **Site** "). Please read the following policy to understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you may provide to us via the Site. This policy may be revised from time to time, so please revisit this page often to remain fully informed of our policies.

APPLICABILITY OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

This Privacy Statement applies only to information submitted and collected through the Site, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Triumph through any other means, including by phone, through postal mail and/or through other live and print media.

WHAT INFORMATION DOES TRIUMPH COLLECT FROM YOU?

Via the Site, Triumph collects from you: (i) personally identifiable information, and (ii) technical and other information.

  * Personally Identifiable Information. 

_General Site Visitors_. When you browse the non-password protected portions of the Site, you do so anonymously; no personally identifiable information is collected. However, if you click on social "plug-ins" on the Site (such as for Facebook or Twitter), those actions will be associated with, and we will have access to, your basic information on those social media sites. For example, if you click on the Facebook icon, we will have access to your name, email, gender, date of birth, current city and profile picture, notwithstanding that you have not registered on the Site. In addition, if you "Like" our Site or any item on the Site on Facebook, our Site will appear in the "Likes" section of your profile, and we will have the ability to publish updates to you.

_Registered Users_. The Site allows you to become a registered user of the Site. If you choose to become a registered user, you will be providing to us your first name, last name, date of birth, email address, mailing address and password. 

_Purchasers_. If you choose to purchase any of our products via the Site, and you do not have a customer account, we require that you provide us at the time of such purchase your first name, last name, date of birth, billing address, shipping address, phone number and email address for such purposes as noted herein. We may also ask for certain product preferences and size information. 

_Subscribers_. The Site permits you to subscribe to our newsletter and to receive emails and other electronic or physical notifications and information regarding new collections, latest lingerie trends, exclusive offers, sweepstakes and specials. When you subscribe to our newsletter via the Site, you must provide us with your first name, last name, email address and date of birth.

_Employment_. Further, the Site allows you to apply for employment positions with Triumph. If you choose to apply for employment via the Site, you will be providing us with your first name, last name, email address, phone number, the information contained in your resume, and any information you choose to provide us about your employment history and/or other relevant information.

_Contacting Us_. The Site permits you to contact us via our online Contact Us form. Whenever you send an email via the online Contact Us form on the Site, you may be providing us with your first name, last name, email address, phone number and any information you choose to include in the text of your message. For example, you may choose to provide your mailing address or other information necessary or helpful for us to address your query or other concern.

_Feedback and Testimonials_. We allow Site users to rate and/or review our products and, in the future, may allow users to post other information or content (" **User Content** "). Such User Content may include testimonials relating to users' personal experiences with Triumph, its products or the Site. As part of such User Content you may be providing us with personally identifiable information, such as your name, location, likeness, voice and other information you choose to make known. 

_Sweepstakes, Contests and Offerings_. From time to time, Triumph may offer you the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes, contests, offers or other activity on or through the Site. If you choose to opt into any such contest, sweepstakes, or other promotion or activity, you may be asked to provide us with certain personally identifiable information necessary to conduct such contest, sweepstakes, or other promotion or activity, such as your name, age, mailing address, email address and phone number. 

  * Technical and Other Information. 

While you are browsing the Site, we automatically log your IP address (a number assigned to your computer when you use the Internet) and your activity while using the Site. Additionally, in order to personalize and enhance your experience on the Site, we may also collect information through "cookies." Cookies are small strings of text that are sent by the Site to your browser and then stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site. We also use cookies to gather broad demographic information and to help identify you in respect to visits to the Site so that we may improve your user experience, and to determine whether you visited the Site from a particular Internet link or advertisement. While a code in the cookie file enables the Site to label you as a particular user, including identifying you by name, address, or other personally identifiable information, such cookie files are encrypted in order to protect your information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but it is possible to change your browser setup so that it does not accept cookies. However, rejecting cookies may prevent you from taking advantage of certain portions of the Site.

  * Google Analytics. 

The Site also may use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (" **Google** "). Google Analytics also uses cookies to help analyze how users use the Site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Site (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Please note that we use Google Analytics with the "_anonymizeIP()" extension, which deletes part of your IP address so it cannot be traced to an individual user. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Site, compiling reports on Site activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. **By using the Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set forth above.**

HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM YOU? 

We collect, retain and use personally identifiable information from you on the Site by expressly requesting it from you (i) when you register for a customer account, (ii) at the time you purchase products through the Site, (iii) when you subscribe to our newsletter, (iv) when you provide User Content through rating, reviews, testimonials and/or otherwise, (v) when you apply for employment with us, (vi) when you click on Facebook, Twitter or other social media "plug-ins" on the Website, (vii) when you request information from us via our online Contact Us form, and (viii) when you participate in contests, sweepstakes and/or other promotions and/or activities.

HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED? 

  * _Our Use of Information_. We collect, retain, and use your personally identifiable information for legitimate business purposes only, including without limitation the following: to facilitate the sale and delivery of our products to purchasers; to operate or improve the Site; to respond to an inquiry from you or address a request submitted by you (including contacting you directly to request additional information to process your inquiry or request); to contact you and to provide you information regarding Triumph and/or our business partners and affiliates; to correspond with you regarding the Site, your orders (e.g., order confirmation, shipping confirmation and/or order cancellation confirmation) or our products; to evaluate your application for employment and to contact you with respect thereto; to inform you of developments in our company or about products that we believe may be of interest; to recognize you as a repeat visitor or customer; to monitor Site visitor traffic patterns and Site usage; to measure or understand the effectiveness of ads you and others see, including to deliver relevant ads to you; to comply with applicable laws, regulations and rules, and requests of relevant law enforcement and/or other governmental agencies; to enforce our Terms of Use; and/or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Triumph, our users, and others.  
As set forth in the [Terms and Conditions] governing the Site, you grant to us, our successors and affiliates, and applicable service providers, a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform, and display all User Content you communicate through the Site, and to incorporate any User Content in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed. We may use any User Content in our business (including, without limitation, for products or advertising) without incurring any liability for royalties or any other consideration of any kind, and will not incur any liability as a result of any similarities that may appear in our future business operations.
  * _Sharing Information_. _We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties_. We share your information only with our service providers (including those managing our Site, or portions or features thereof, and third party payment processors) or as otherwise described herein in order to provide you with our products and/or services. In addition, we may share your information with our affiliated companies for internal business purposes. Also, we may share in aggregate, statistical form, non-personal information regarding the visitors to the Site, traffic patterns, Site usage and ratings and reviews with our partners, service providers, affiliates or advertisers. For example, Triumph may use ad networks to customize and display advertising on the Site. In connection therewith, Triumph may share certain information about you as a customer of Triumph (such as age, zip code, or other information we have collected or received) with certain ad network and service providers to help them deliver more relevant content and advertisements through their networks. Further, we will disclose information we maintain, including personally identifiable information, when required to do so by law, or may disclose such information in response to a request from a law enforcement agency or authority.
  * _Third Party Payment Processors_. If you choose to purchase products available via the Site using our third party payment processors, you may be required to provide personally identifiable information to credit card companies, PayPal or other third party payment processors for the purpose of facilitating the payment for your purchase. The privacy of such information is subject to the privacy policies and procedures of such credit card companies, PayPal or other third party payment processors. 

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES AND SERVICES

Triumph may reference, provide links to or include features or functionality on the Site that connect or link to third party websites, services or servers. We are not responsible for these third party websites, services and servers, and you should review the privacy policies posted on such sites or otherwise available for such services. In this regard, as noted above, to the extent any credit card payment information (including the number, security code and expiration date) is submitted by you in connection with your use of the Site, such information is not collected by Triumph but rather is sent directly to a third party payment processor. In addition, we use a third party service provider in connection with our ratings and review feature on our Site and such provider collects user information from the Site. The applicable privacy policy for the service provider providing the ratings and review feature can be found at <http://bazaarvoice.com/privacy-policy>. Triumph may use additional service providers, which similarly collect user information and have their own privacy policies, to provide specific Site features or functionality in the future. Please be aware that Triumph does not control, nor are we responsible for, the privacy policies or information practices of any such third parties (such as third party payment processors or providers of our ratings and review feature or other features) or their websites or services. **By using a specific feature or functionality, you consent to the transfer, collection and use of your information to or by the third party service provider providing such feature or functionality**.

MODIFICATIONS

We strive to maintain the accuracy of any personally identifiable information that may be collected from you, and will use our commercially reasonable efforts to respond promptly to update our database when you tell us the information in our database is not accurate. It is your responsibility to ensure that such information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you wish to make any changes to any personally identifiable information you have provided to us, you may do so at any time by logging into your customer account, if applicable, and making any such changes, or by contacting us via email at [info@shop-us.triumph.com.](mailto:info@shop-us.triumph.com)

OPT IN / OPT OUT

The Site allows you to opt in to receive our newsletter and/or other information and materials from us and our affiliates regarding our products and services. If you choose to opt in to receive such materials or communications, you may at any time opt out of receiving such materials and communications by following the opt-out link provided in any email received. Please note, however, that after you unsubscribe from our newsletter, we may still need to contact you with important transactional information related to your account and/or products you have purchased. For example, even if you have unsubscribed from our newsletter, we will still send you emails confirming your account preferences.

CONSEQUENCES OF NOT PROVIDING INFORMATION

You may choose not to provide us with your personally identifiable information. However, choosing not to provide certain requested personally identifiable information may prevent you from accessing and taking advantage of certain products and/or services offered by Triumph.

CHILDREN

This Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. Accordingly, in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, 15 U.S.C. §§ 6501-06 and 16 C.F.R. §§ 312.1-312.12, we will not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age. In addition, we do not permit children under 18 years of age to purchase products or to register for an account on the Site. **_By using the Site, you represent that you are not under 13 years of age. Further, by registering for an account with Triumph and/or purchasing products via the Site, you represent that you are at least 18 years of age, and have the right to form legally binding contracts and to perform your obligations hereunder_**. 

PROTECTING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Because security is important to both Triumph and you, we maintain data handling and storage practices and procedures that are designed to maintain the integrity and confidentiality of the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Industry standard Internet security methods and technologies, such as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, are used in an effort to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. SSL encrypts the transmissions from our ecommerce servers as well as your computer. SSL encryption works by forming a matched pair with the transmission from your computer transmission and our server, so that only data to and from these sources can be valid. If you are a registered user, typically, information associated with your account will be kept until your account is deleted. For certain categories of data, we may also tell you from time to time about specific data retention practices. You should not share your account password with anyone. In addition, if you suspect unauthorized access to your account information, it is your responsibility to contact Triumph immediately. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or the policies of the Site and our service providers).

BUSINESS TRANSFER

Triumph may, in the future, sell or otherwise transfer some or all of its assets to a third party. Your personally identifiable information and/or technical information we obtain from you via the Site may be disclosed to any potential or actual third party purchasers of such assets and/or may be among those assets transferred.

ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS 

This Privacy Statement is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Triumph Terms of Use. By using the Site and voluntarily providing your personally identifiable information to us, you consent to the collection and use of such personally identifiable information as set forth in this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, please do not provide us with any information and do not use the Site.

INTERNATIONAL USERS - APPLICABLE LAW

We collect, process, store, use, disclose, and dispose of personal information that you submit to us in accordance with applicable United States law. Please note that the personal information you submit to our Site will be transferred to the United States to be processed by us in order to provide the Site and our services to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Privacy Statement. If you are not a resident of the United States, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect, process, store, use, disclose and dispose your personal information, as discussed in this Privacy Statement, outside your resident jurisdiction, and it is your responsibility for ensuring whether such actions and the sharing of information with Triumph through the Site conforms to all local data protection laws applicable to you. In this regard, please be aware that United States law may offer different levels of protection for personal information than may be available in your country.

EFFECTIVENESS

This Privacy Statement is effective as of the "Last Updated" date on the first page of this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this policy, and any such modifications, alterations, or updates will be effective upon posting. In the event we modify this Privacy Statement, your continued use of the Site will signify your acceptance of the modified Privacy Statement.

QUESTIONS?

Questions regarding this Privacy Statement should be directed to [info@shop-us.triumph.com](mailto:info@shop-us.triumph.com). Triumph may also be contacted directly at the following address and phone number: 

Triumph of Europe, Inc.  
530 Seventh Avenue  
Suite 1006   
New York, New York 10018  
Phone: (212) 302-2606
